frontrowshop.com 2016-03-14

# Front Row Shop - Home

## Privacy Policy

FrontRowShop respects your privacy and takes your online safety seriously. In order to provide you with the best products, efficient customer service, and timely updates, we record a variety of information from your visit on our Website. To better protect your privacy, we provide the notice below explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**FrontRowShop's Privacy Policy**

Thank you for accessing the website of Shanghai Front Row e-Commerce Co., Ltd. (all references to “us”, “we”, “Website” and “our" refer to FrontRowShop.com). We respect your privacy and want you to know about the policies we have in place to protect your personal information.

This Privacy Policy explains:

How we collect, use, and (under certain conditions) disclose personal information.

The steps we’ve taken to secure personal information.

Your options regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information.

This Privacy Notice applies only to this website and does not necessarily apply to personal information we collect from you offline. Please see the section on Offline Collection, Use & Disclosure of Information details. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any website other than FrontRowShop.com to which the Website links or that links to FrontRowShop.com.

By visiting our website, you accept the practices described in this Notice.

How does FrontRowShop.com collect information?

How does FrontRowShop.com use personal information? 

How are cookies and other technologies used to collect information?

Does FrontRowShop.com ever give out personal information?

Is information FrontRowShop.com collects secure?

Are children allowed to use FrontRowShop.com?

How does FrontRowShop.com use and disclose information collected offline?

Where can website users find updates to this policy?

How does FrontRowShop.com collect information?

We collect information from Website users in several different ways, with the goal of providing an efficient, meaningful, and customized shopping experience. For example, we can use personal information to: 

  * Record and quickly bring up information users have given previously

  * Help users quickly find information, products, and services

  * Create content that is relevant to users

  * Alert users of our new information, products, and services

Registration and Ordering: In order to use certain parts of the Website or order products, all customers must fill out an online registration form with personal information, including but not limited to, your name, gender, shipping and billing address(es), phone number, email address, and credit card number. In addition, we may ask for your country of residence and/or your organization's country of operation, so that we can comply with applicable laws and regulations. This information is used for billing, order processing and internal marketing as well as communicating with you about your order and our website.

Email Addresses: Several locations on the Website allow you to enter your email address for purposes including but not limited to: registering for free promotional notices, requesting notification when new brands or product styles arrive, or signing up for our email newsletter. In addition, any participation in promotional contests organized by FrontRowShop.com is completely voluntary and requires disclosure of contact information needed to notify winners and award prizes. We may post the names and cities of contest winners on our Website or our relevant public accounts.

How does FrontRowShop.com use cookies and other technology to collect information?

Cookies are small pieces of information that your Internet browser stores as text files on your computer's hard drive. Most browsers accept cookies by default, but setting your browser to refuse cookies or removing them from your hard drive will prevent you from using parts of this Website. FrontRowShop.com uses cookies to:

   * Speed up navigation 

   * Track Website usage

   * Recognize users and user access privileges

   * Enable selection and purchase products on this Website to record your browsing activity and purchases

We may use content or ads from third-party advertising companies that may use cookies and web beacons to measure web page visits or amount of products purchased. Any information these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is not linked to any personal information we collect.

Internal Use: We use personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may use your personal information internally to collect general information about visitors to this Website, improve Website content and layout, improve our outreach, and market our services and products.

Communication with You: We will use your personal information to communicate with you about our Website and your orders. All customers must provide an email address to allow communication with FrontRowShop.com regarding orders placed. We may send you a confirmation email after you register with us as well as service-related announcements when necessary (for example, temporary suspension of service for maintenance). You may also submit your email address to request notification when we receive a new brand, product style or product, or to sign up for our email newsletter and special offers. You can unsubscribe or opt out of future emails at any time.

Does FrontRowShop.com ever give out personal information?

We sell merchandise, not information — we do not sell, rent, trade, license, or otherwise disclose your personal or financial information to anyone, except in the following specific situations:

Third-party service providers: Like most online retailers, we sometimes use third-party service providers to perform specific functions on our behalf. Any information disclosed to them is solely to help with their provision of service. For example, we provide your name, shipping address, email and phone number to partners such as DHL and UPS in order to guarantee delivery of your orders, and we may use relevant customer information in order to monitor the quality of the third party’s service.

Similarly, we must provide your credit card number to financial services organizations such as credit card processors and issuers in order to process payments. We protect all submissions of your credit card number for authorization with state-of-the-art data encryption.

Legal requirement to disclose information: We may be required to disclose information if subpoenaed, served with a court order or requested by law-enforcement officials conducting investigations, or if we are otherwise required by law to disclose such information. We will also release personal information when necessary to protect our legal rights or enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements. For example, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud, or to prevent fraud by users who attempt fraud or other illegal activity on our Website.

Merger and/or sale of assets: We do not normally sell, trade or rent personal information to other companies in the course of our business. However, it is possible that we might acquire, merge with or be acquired by another company, or that we might dispose of some or all of our assets, in which case your personal information could be disclosed to another company, subject to the Privacy Notice in effect.

Non-personally identifiable information: We may share information that does not identify you or any user, such as the number of daily visitors to a particular page, or the size of an order placed on a certain date, with third parties such as advertising partners.

How does FrontRowShop.com secure information collected?

The Website incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as:

  * Safeguarding all financial transactions done through this Website with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption 

  * Granting only employees who are providing a specific service access to your personal information 

  * Working only with third-party service providers who we believe adequately secure all computer hardware.

While our business is designed with safeguarding your personal information in mind, please remember that 100% security does not presently exist anywhere, online or offline.

What choices do I have regarding FrontRowShop.com’s collection of personal information?

You can choose to: 

   * Correct or update your personal information 

   * Stop receiving email to your email address 

   * Disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account

To correct or update your personal information, log in to My Accounts and then change your Account Information. To unsubscribe from emails you receive from FrontRowShop.com, log in to My Account and then untick Newletter Subscriptions.

Are children allowed to use FrontRowShop.com?

We respect children's privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 13. Elsewhere on this Website, you have represented and warranted that you are either 18 years of age or are using the Website with the supervision of a parent or guardian.

If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you when using the Website.

How does FrontRowShop.com use and disclose information collected offline?

As FrontRowShop.com collects most information through the Website, this Privacy Policy applies only to online collection of personal information.

We also protect all personal information that is collected from you offline, such as through phone calls. If we contact you by telephone regarding an order or payment, we will ask only for the personal information needed to place your order or resolve your issue. When we need to store information related to an order, we enter it into our database through SSL encryption.

This Policy does not attempt to cover all possible offline methods of collecting or using personal information, however, we will treat any offline collection, use, or disclosure of personal information in a manner consistent with our online practices.

Where can I find updates to this policy?

To keep you informed of what information we collect, use, and disclose, we will post any changes or updates to this Privacy Notice on this Website or send you an email regarding updates to the Privacy Notice and encourage you to review this Privacy Notice from time to time. Please contact us with any questions about the Privacy Notice.
